<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:nyt="http://www.nytimes.com/namespaces/rss/2.0" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Hac3dBlog &gt; Recent</title>
    <link>https://www.hac3d.com/?cfdone</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.hac3d.com/rss/default.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
    <description></description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Hac3d's Blog, duh.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 21:12:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 21:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <image>
      <title>Hac3dBlog &gt; Recent</title>
      <url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/misc/NYT_logo_rss_250x40.png</url>
      <link>https://www.hac3d.com/?cfdone</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>REGGIE! -- A blog about today’s memes</title>
      <link>https://www.hac3d.com/article/reggie</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.hac3d.com/article/reggie</guid>
      <atom:link href="https://www.hac3d.com/article/reggie" rel="standout"></atom:link>
      <description>I hate my life lol. This meme is basically just a photo of this guy and someone screaming his name. It scared the shit out of me the first time I saw it. I was scrolling through my feed late at night, and suddenly, this loud voice shouted "REGGIE!" I nearly dropped my phone.

The meme's origins are kind of mysterious, but that hasn't stopped it from spreading like wildfire. It's everywhere now, from Twitter to TikTok, and even on random YouTube videos. The guy in the photo? No one really knows who he is, but he has this confused, almost panicked expression that makes the whole thing even funnier.

The meme has inspired countless variations. Some people have edited it to scream different names or phrases, and others have added it to famous movie scenes for an extra dose of chaos. There's even a subreddit dedicated to the "REGGIE!" meme, where fans share their favorite versions and new, creative takes on it.

Despite the simplicity of the meme, or maybe because of it, "REGGIE!" has become a cultural phenomenon. It's a reminder that sometimes the internet's most beloved content is born from the most unexpected and random places.

So, what do you think about the "REGGIE!" meme? Love it? Hate it? Drop a comment below and let me know your thoughts!

Stay meme-tastic,
Hac3d</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 19:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category domain="">Supreme Courts (State)</category>
      <category domain="">Decisions and Verdicts</category>
      <category domain="">Wisconsin</category>
      <category domain="">Voting and Voters</category>
      <category domain="">Absentee Voting</category>
      <media:content height="1800" medium="image" url="https://static01.nyt.com/images/2024/07/05/multimedia/05nat-wisconsin-court-lbwz/05nat-wisconsin-court-lbwz-mediumSquareAt3X.jpg" width="1800"></media:content>
      <media:credit>Lauren Justice for The New York Times</media:credit>
      <media:description>A man uses a ballot drop box at a fire station in Madison, Wis., in 2020. Wide use of the boxes in that election led to efforts by conservatives to restrict them.</media:description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>