<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:nyt="http://www.nytimes.com/namespaces/rss/2.0" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Hac3dBlog &gt; Recent</title>
	<logo>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Hac3d/hac3dblog-rss/main/images/icon.ico</logo>
    <link>https://www.hac3d.com/?cfdone</link>
	<icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Hac3d/hac3dblog-rss/main/images/icon.ico</icon>
    <atom:link href="https://www.hac3d.com/rss/default.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
	<atom:icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Hac3d/hac3dblog-rss/main/images/icon.ico</atom:icon>
    <description></description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Hac3d's Blog, duh.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 21:12:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 21:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <image>
      <title>Hac3dBlog &gt; Recent</title>
      <url>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Hac3d/hac3dblog-rss/main/images/icon.ico</url>
      <link>https://www.hac3d.com/?cfdone</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>REGGIE! -- A blog about today’s memes</title>
      <link>https://www.hac3d.com/article/reggie</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.hac3d.com/article/reggie</guid>
      <atom:link href="https://www.hac3d.com/article/reggie" rel="standout"></atom:link>
	  <likes>15</likes>
      <description>I hate my life lol. This meme is basically just a photo of this guy (the photo if ur using rss) and someone screaming his name. It scared the shit out of me the first time I saw it. I was scrolling through my feed late at night, and suddenly, this loud voice shouted "REGGIE!" I nearly dropped my phone.

The meme's origins are kind of mysterious, but that hasn't stopped it from spreading like wildfire. It's everywhere now, from Twitter to TikTok, and even on random YouTube videos. The guy in the photo? No one really knows who he is, but he has this confused, almost panicked expression that makes the whole thing even funnier.

The meme has inspired countless variations. Some people have edited it to scream different names or phrases, and others have added it to famous movie scenes for an extra dose of chaos. There's even a subreddit dedicated to the "REGGIE!" meme, where fans share their favorite versions and new, creative takes on it.

Despite the simplicity of the meme, or maybe because of it, "REGGIE!" has become a cultural phenomenon. It's a reminder that sometimes the internet's most beloved content is born from the most unexpected and random places.

So, what do you think about the "REGGIE!" meme? Love it? Hate it? Drop a comment below and let me know your thoughts!

Stay meme-tastic,
Hac3d</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 19:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category domain="">Posted by: Hac3d (real) On: 6/5/2024</category>
	  <category domain="">Edited on 7/5/2024</category>
      <media:content height="1800" medium="image" url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Hac3d/hac3dblog-rss/main/images/reggie.png" width="1800"></media:content>
      <media:credit>Hac3d</media:credit>
      <media:description>I hate my life lol. This meme is basically just a photo of this guy and someone screaming his name.</media:description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Bitches? -- A blog about yesterday’s memes</title>
      <link>https://www.hac3d.com/article/nobitches</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.hac3d.com/article/nobitches</guid>
      <atom:link href="https://www.hac3d.com/article/nobitches" rel="standout"></atom:link>
      <description>I keep seeing this meme everywhere so I decided to make a post about it lol.
This meme is like the reggie to the Skibidi Toilet meme. While "REGGIE!" was all about the shock value and absurdity, "No Bitches?" plays on a more sarcastic and mocking tone.

The meme typically features the classic "smallbrain" character with the phrase "NO BITCHES?" in bold text above it. It's usually used to respond to posts or comments in a way that's meant to be dismissive or critical, often implying that the person being addressed is socially inept or unsuccessful in their romantic endeavors. 

The origins of the meme trace back to early 2024, when it first appeared on Twitter. It quickly gained traction due to its simplicity and versatility. People began to use it in various contexts, creating countless variations that addressed different situations and personalities. Some versions even feature different characters or altered text to fit specific scenarios, but the core message remains the same.

What makes "No Bitches?" so popular is its relatability and the universal appeal of humor that borders on the offensive yet stays just playful enough to be widely accepted. It's the kind of meme that can make you laugh or groan, depending on how it's used and who it's directed at.

Despite its seemingly harsh tone, many people find the meme amusing and enjoy the creative ways it has been adapted. It's another example of how internet culture can take a simple idea and turn it into something much bigger.

So, what's your take on the "No Bitches?" meme? Do you think it's funny or just plain rude? Share your thoughts in the comments below!

Stay meme-tastic,
Hac3d</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2024 19:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category domain="">Posted by: Hac3d (real) On: 6/5/2024</category>
      <media:content height="1800" medium="image" url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Hac3d/hac3dblog-rss/main/images/nobitches.png" width="1800"></media:content>
      <media:credit>Hac3d</media:credit>
      <media:description>I keep seeing this meme everywhere so I decided to make a post about it lol. This meme is like the reggie to the skibid...</media:description>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Moving! -- A blog about updates to the blog</title>
  <link>https://www.hac3d.com/article/moving</link>
  <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.hac3d.com/article/moving</guid>
  <atom:link href="https://www.hac3d.com/article/moving" rel="standout"></atom:link>
  <description>Yes, I know I travelled back in time, But this is important lol. I had to move the site URL since the API re-write broke the domain to pieces. 

After the latest update, the old URL was no longer functional, and it caused quite a few issues for our regular readers. I know it was frustrating, and I appreciate everyone's patience during this transition. 

The new site URL is now live, and everything should be back to normal. You'll find all the same great content and more, but with improved performance and a cleaner interface. Make sure to update your bookmarks to the new address: https://www.hac3d.com

We have a lot of exciting updates planned for the coming months, including new features, more frequent posts, and a few surprises. Stay tuned!

Thank you for sticking with us through this change. Your support means the world to me.

Stay meme-tastic,
Hac3d</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  <category domain="">Posted by: Hac3d (real) On: 17/05/2024</category>
  <media:credit>Hac3d</media:credit>
  <media:description>Yes, I know I travelled back in time, But this is important lol. I had to move the site URL since the API re-write broke the domain to piec...</media:description>
</item>

<item>
  <title>RSS support?! -- A blog about updates to the blog</title>
  <link>https://www.hac3d.com/article/rss-support</link>
  <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.hac3d.com/article/rss-support</guid>
  <atom:link href="https://www.hac3d.com/article/rss-support" rel="standout"></atom:link>
  <description>Yes, I know I travelled back in time, again, But this is also important lol. I also stole that from the moving post, haha. I've added RSS to the blog cuz people wanted it.

Many of you have been asking for RSS support for a while now, and I'm happy to announce that it's finally here! You can now subscribe to the blog's RSS feed and get updates delivered straight to your feed reader of choice. This should make it a lot easier to keep up with the latest posts, especially if you prefer using an RSS reader over checking the site manually.

To subscribe, just add this URL to your RSS reader: https://www.hac3d.com/rss. It's that simple! 

In addition to RSS support, I've made a few other minor improvements to the site based on your feedback. The navigation is now more intuitive, and the loading times should be faster, becuz I upgraded the server.

As always, I appreciate your continued support and feedback. If you have any other suggestions or requests, feel free to drop a comment or reach out to me directly.

The RSS feed can be accessed on github here: https://hac3d.github.io/hac3dblog-rss/recent.xml
thx for the support :)

Stay meme-tastic,
Hac3d</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
  <category domain="">Posted by: Hac3d (real) On: July 5, 2024</category>
  <media:credit>Hac3d</media:credit>
  <media:description>Yes, I know I travelled back in time, again, But this is also important lol. I also stole that from the moving post, haha. I've added RSS to the blog cuz people wanted it...</media:description>
</item>


  </channel>
</rss>